wahgifts.com 2015-12-07

# WahGifts.com - Privacy Policy

We understand your concern about the personal information you submit on our web-site. We also go by the notion that has to be a fine equilibrium between the need to give better, tailored and customized service to you and to protect your personal details, simultaneously [www.wahgifts.com](http://www.wahgifts.com/) value your trust in us that we shall not misuse your personal information in any way.

You can visit the Site and explore our offerings without submitting any personal details. During your visit to the Site you are anonymous and we could not discover you unless you have an account on the Site and log on with your user name and password.

Data that we collect

We may collect little information if you place an order for a product to us on the Site. We gather your data only for processing your order on [www.wahgifts.com](http://www.wahgifts.com/) & any possible future claims & offer you our services.It might be possible that we collect your name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), contact number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details.

Basically, we need the information to process the payment for the product(s) & deliver the product at your doorsteps. We also use the data to inform you about the possible time when the product is to be delivered.

At times, we may share your name & address on to a third party, (for example to our courier or supplier) to deliver the product to you. We may also share your data with our franchisor. You further authorize the franchisor to use this information to sell products to you, directly or indirectly. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

Cookies

Like many online services, [www.wahgifts.com](http://www.wahgifts.com/) uses “cookies” on our portal to gather information. A cookie is a small text file that is transferred to your computer or mobile device’s hard disk when you visit a website. We use cookies for two things. Firstly, we use “persistent” cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Service. Second, we employ “session ID” cookies to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor the web traffic routing on the Service. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Service and then close your browser.

Consent

By submitting data to us, you allow us to use your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

Links with other sites

Our site may contain some links which may take you to some other websites which may have their own privacy policy, different from ours. It means that once you leave our site, our privacy policy will no longer apply.
